{
    "subject": "resource/Babyface_(musician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Babyface's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9039588570594788,
            "question": "Babyface's hometown is in North America. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8513692617416382,
            "question": "In the United States, where was Babyface born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8327013254165649,
            "question": "Is Babyface originally from a place outside of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8132402300834656,
            "question": "Does Babyface's hometown have a specific city or state associated with it?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7862939238548279,
            "question": "What country is considered Babyface's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7106810212135315,
            "question": "Babyface's hometown is a country. What is that country called?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6256669163703918,
            "question": "Where is Babyface from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6132579445838928,
            "question": "Besides the United States, are there any other countries that Babyface is known to be from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2754303812980652,
            "question": "Can you tell me where Babyface grew up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13403891026973724,
            "question": "What is the name of the country that Babyface calls home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Babyface's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9299_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me where Babyface grew up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9299_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides the United States, are there any other countries that Babyface is known to be from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9299_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Babyface from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9299_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9299_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Babyface is from Indianapolis, Indiana, United States of America. Therefore, it supports the statement that Babyface's hometown is in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states Babyface's hometown is the United States, but multiple sources clearly state he is from Indianapolis, Indiana within the United States.  This indicates his hometown is a specific city, not the entire country.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}